Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employees Reports 5514
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employees Reports
1923-1926
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Railroad Labor Board
5514
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Earning records from the Train and Engine Service Employes.
5658971
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 28, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Wages -- Railroads -- United States.; United States Railroad Labor Board.
5658971
- US Railroad Labor Board. Correspondence of the Chairman, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  July 30, 1925; August 13, 1925; August 22, 1925; August 29, 1925; September 11, 1925.
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes. Volume 1. Road and Assistant Conductors, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  June 1925
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 2. Train Baggage men and Passenger Brakemen, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  July 1925
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 3. Freight Brakemen, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 4. Yard Foremen and Yard Helpers, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  August 1925
- Earnings Covering Calendar Year 1923. Switchtenders. Volume 5, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employees Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 6. Passenger and Freight Engineers, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Earnings Covering Calendar Year 1923. Yard Engineers. Volume 7, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  September 1925
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 8. Passenger Firemen, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 10. Yard Firemen, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  October 1925
- Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employes Covering Calendar Year 1923. Volume 12. General Index and Recapitulation, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  January 1926